<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version='2.0'>
  <channel>
    <title>Tumblr Dashboard</title>
    <link>http://tumblr.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>alaskamiller: My friend Dan was such a prick. Don&#821...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://30.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ky01rzECSP1qz7rt0o1_250.jpg"></p><p>My friend Dan was such a prick. Don&#8217;t let the fact that he still sips Elmer&#8217;s glue in second grade deter you from calling him a retard; he doesn&#8217;t do that for attention, he just liked the way it swooshed in his mouth. What a fucking Palin.</p>
            <p>But Dan&#8217;s dad was super duper rich so playground rules dictated we had to be nice to Dan, because after we&#8217;re all done swinging on swings and monkey around on monkey bars Dan got to choose who he takes home to play Super Mario World on a Trinitron. Tragically enough, it was never the girls.</p>
            <p>I didn&#8217;t even know what this game was about but I just knew I had to beat it. I&#8217;ve been playing the same ten JAWS games on my NES my whole life and according to Nintendo Power, no fucking armies of koopas and centipedes or wayward shells should stop me from saving the princess. None. Except some brat named Dan. I wasn&#8217;t going to take his verbal and physical abuse like the others to play Mario so I went to my other friend Chris&#8212;he liked Star Trek so I liked Star Trek and not Star Wars&#8212;and we spent one recess creating a dastardly elaborate plan to maximize our Christmases: we got our parents to agree to split and buy us a SNES.</p>
            <p>Chris had it first because unbeknown to me my mom wasn&#8217;t able to chip in. Chris&#8217; parents simply gave me the SNES for free after Chris was bored with it after a few months. And also &#8216;cause he had some weird fetish for locking his sister outside the house. I was too young to care about pity, or maybe I did, but having a SNES is a pretty fucking big deal enough to stuff childhood emotions into dark closets and just focus on the mission at hand: the princess.</p>
            <p>I played this game so hard I broke the controller. Now no one can play Luigi with me but I didn&#8217;t care. I&#8217;m going to win this myself and I&#8217;m going to head to that scary pirate ship swirl thing in the center and I&#8217;m going to upfuck Bowser&#8217;s little world. I had swagger then, from playing Mario. Don&#8217;t tell me about the fucking stripes and stars on the flag, old white lady, I have a manifest destiny to save the princess.</p>
            <p>I breezed through the worlds. The frustration is of course each of the boss fortresses didn&#8217;t contain the princess. And it just aggravated me to no end, though at the same time made me want to finish everything as soon as I can. Forest of Illusion gave me the most trouble but the princess. Oh, how she cried out to me in the middle of the night from from the family room, through the cheap and shitty US-made TV.</p>
            <p>Three months after it&#8217;s all been said and done, on a Wednesday, I finally finished the FINAL BOSS. I was proud, I ran through every level and stomped on every turtle and I got a kiss from the princess for my troubles. I walked up to Dan after school when he was ready to seduce more young boys to play Home Alone with him and told him said fact&#8212;that it was lame he&#8217;s picking boys to play home alone&#8212;and to brag about how I beat Mario in three months. I also wanted to tell him that his Talkboy is lame despite how much I wanted one too but didn&#8217;t get around to it. Dan looked at me for a bit, mumbled into his Talkboy and played it back to me: &#8220;You&#8217;re so stupid, I finished it two days by using Star World.&#8221;</p>
            <p>Fuck you, Dan. What the fuck is Star World?</p>
            <p>&#8220;Haha! Stupid! It&#8217;s the top-secret shortcut in Vanilla Dome that takes you directly to the castle. No wonder you didn&#8217;t know about it, cause you&#8217;re just too dumb.&#8221; In slow-mo.</p>
            <p>I&#8217;m left stunned as Dan and his little goons went away. This was a turning point, those goons later grew up to be the worst bullies in school by the time I moved away. I went home thinking I should replay this game, to hit the secret world and really get the satisfaction of finishing a video game that took me much more energy and planning in real life to get in the first place because otherwise I just feel&#8230; incomplete.</p>
            <p>The bothered me for so long but I couldn&#8217;t pick up the controller. Why would the princess not tell me about the Star World? It would have been so much easier. After a week I rode on my Huffy down the valley to give the SNES back to Chris. He seemed happy for it to be back in his life but I couldn&#8217;t tell. He offered to play Mario with me but I told him no, thanks, the princess is dead to me. That and the other controller doesn&#8217;t work.</p>
            <p>I didn&#8217;t care when the 64 came out. I didn&#8217;t get the PlayStation. The Dreamcast didn&#8217;t entice me. And since I didn&#8217;t live in a dorm or a frat, I never cared about Halo. It just didn&#8217;t trigger anything.</p>
            <p>So don&#8217;t tell me let&#8217;s just be friends. It&#8217;s already ruined. I know you have a Star World map. I know it. It&#8217;s the secret place that contains all your secrets, stories, and heartbreaks. I want to engage that level and I want to complete this game. Telling me let&#8217;s just keep it Yoshi&#8217;s Island isn&#8217;t so simple when I want to be in your Chocolate Island, explore your Donut Plains, cross your Butter Bridge, and complete the special Star Roads. Otherwise, what&#8217;s the point? You constantly hide, every now and then scaring the shit out of me, and continuing to haunt me.</p>
            <p>You&#8217;re my Big Boo.</p>
            <p>PS. I still hate you, Dan. I don&#8217;t care if you&#8217;re going to HBS now and will likely end up making millions corrupting humanity, you&#8217;re still a just glue eater to me.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>m0rganamian: I AM ALL ABOUT THIS.</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://m0rganamian.tumblr.com/photo/1280/395517998/1/tumblr_ky0fzepjuq1qa9vpz"></p><p>I AM ALL ABOUT <a href="http://www.thesartorialist.blogspot.com/">THIS</a>.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>youmightfindyourself:  Dead End</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ky0fh8IeFI1qzu6nxo1_500.jpg"></p><p><a href="http://johnchagaris.wordpress.com/2010/01/14/304/#respond" target="_blank"> Dead End</a></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>irondavy: Ad I did for the wonderful MaxFunCon. I&...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://29.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ky0fg6xliY1qzwfzfo1_500.png"></p><p>Ad I did for the wonderful <a href="http://www.maxfuncon.com/" target="_blank">MaxFunCon</a>. I&#8217;m going, won&#8217;t you join me!?</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>wreckandsalvage: Vancouver 2010 Olympics Photos by Duncan...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://blog.wreckandsalvage.com/photo/1280/395488793/1/tumblr_ky0f6nk4EF1qz515b"></p><p><a href="http://thelastminuteblog.com/2010/02/06/vancouver-olympics-photos/" target="_blank">Vancouver 2010 Olympics Photos</a></p>
            <p>by Duncan Rawlinson. Lots of great photos on the page, let em all load.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>david: via theinternetaccordingtoadrian and po...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://www.davidslog.com/photo/1280/395478204/1/tumblr_ky0d6gkBFe1qza3e8"></p><p>via <a href="http://theinternetaccordingtoadrian.tumblr.com/">theinternetaccordingtoadrian</a> and <a href="http://poobah.tumblr.com/post/395474614/via-theinternetaccordingtoadrian">poobah</a></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>merlin: From Paul&#8217;s letter to the church i...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://27.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ky0erb39dE1qz4rlzo1_400.jpg"></p><p>From Paul&#8217;s letter to the church in Rome:</p>
            
            <blockquote>
              <p>For I am not ashamed of the gospel of Christ: for it is the power of God unto salvation to every one that believeth; to the Jew first, and also to the Gentile.</p>
            </blockquote>
            
            <p>I also hear it&#8217;s easier for a camel to pass through the eye of a needle than for me to use your God-fearing wifi to download this one fucking Of Montreal song I really want to hear.</p>
            
            <p>That&#8217;s from &#8220;Matthew WPA:2.&#8221;  Look it up.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dalasverdugo: arachno - wings over dunwyn Feels like S...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p>arachno - wings over dunwyn</p>
            <p>Feels like Spring today!</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>staff: Universal Record Database: Most Notes On...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            Universal Record Database: Most Notes On A Single Tumblr Post
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>john: Tumblr Staff: Dashboard API: Part 1</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            Tumblr Staff: Dashboard API: Part 1
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>curvedwhite: Revel Cabinet by Studiomama</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://curvedwhite.com/photo/1280/395428253/1/tumblr_kxy6d8M3Er1qatctm"></p><p><a href="http://www.studiomama.com/reveal.html">Revel Cabinet</a> by <a href="http://www.studiomama.com/">Studiomama</a></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>david: I must confess: In that last photo, I wa...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p>I must confess: In that <a href="http://www.davidslog.com/395408815/thats-a-big-ass-camera">last photo</a>, I was compelled to crop Microsoft Word out of my Dock.</p>
            <p>I probably only had it open because of some stupid file <a href="http://jaredhecht.com/">Jared</a> sent me.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>youmightfindyourself: made you look, two hits.</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ky0d2lnnfM1qzu6nxo1_400.jpg"></p><p>made you look, two hits.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>meaghano: housingworksbookstore: OMG stop rebloggi...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://meaghano.com/photo/1280/395410425/1/tumblr_ky0ctwQcFZ1qb6ut5"></p><p><a href="http://housingworksbookstore.tumblr.com/post/395404111/omg-stop-reblogging-the-picture-of-our-ugly-1" target="_blank">housingworksbookstore</a>:</p>
            <blockquote>
            <p>OMG stop reblogging the picture of our ugly $1 cart. We are so pretty, see??</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>HAH.</p>
            <p>LOOK AT THIS FUCKING BOOKSTORE. LOOK AT IT.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>david: It&#8217;s cool. I&#8217;m used to it.</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://28.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ky0cyskabq1qz4rgqo1_500.png"></p><p>It&#8217;s cool. I&#8217;m used to it.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>staff: Dashboard API: Part 1</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            Dashboard API: Part 1
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>meaghano: housingworksbookstore: “Easily one of ...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://meaghano.com/photo/1280/395375629/1/tumblr_ky07j0VnHm1qb6ut5"></p><p><a href="http://housingworksbookstore.tumblr.com/post/395219410/easily-one-of-my-favorite-spots-in-the-city" target="_blank">housingworksbookstore</a>:</p>
            <blockquote>
            <p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/amanda_munoz/4365844884/" target="_blank">“Easily one of my favorite spots in the city. Located in SoHo, I’m  constantly in there picking up books off of the $0.50 rack or $2.00  vinyl records. The coffee is fantastic, they host free events all the  time, and all of the profits go to the Housing Works foundation, which  works to physically house people suffering from HIV/AIDS as well as  spread awareness.”</a></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Look who got a Tumblr!</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>alaskamiller: You know what&#8217;s funny is how good ...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://30.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ky0bmeMhjy1qz7rt0o1_400.jpg"></p><p>You know what&#8217;s funny is how good board games are at telling you what life is going to be like. Monopoly explains greed. Operation teaches you not to touch the sides. And Sorry shows that your buddies are vengeful dickwads.</p>
            <p>Then you get to thinking that The Game of Life might really be what life would be like if you never got the joy of playing the Sims for the whole weekend straight. Then you start to fantasize maybe this is how it&#8217;ll be: find a pink peg, settle down, have more pegs in the car, and end up happy because you stacked the life event cards to your favor before everyone sat down.</p>
            <p>But it&#8217;s not. And so it got me thinking to how to better the experience and I think I got it. Staple a LIFE game board to the bottom of a <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YVz4RR2rw7w" target="_blank">Girl Talk</a> board and to beat the whole thing you just have to be really good at football. That&#8217;s how you win life.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bbook: Pegasus mating with a unicorn and the cr...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            Pegasus mating with a unicorn and the creature that they birth I somehow tame it and ride it to the sky and clouds and sunshine and rainbows. That’s how I feel.
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ckck: As flattering as it is to see your own w...</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <p><img src="http://26.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ky0a6pgoBr1qz4hjyo1_500.jpg"></p><p>As flattering as it is to see <a href="http://ckck.tumblr.com/post/225173901/jackson-wyoming">your</a> <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/zerogrizzly/4225979932/in/set-72157594539473428/">own</a> work being appreciated by others, it isn&#8217;t fun when you don&#8217;t get credit for it.</p>
            <p>Via <a href="http://artsandcrafts.tumblr.com/">artsandcrafts</a> (who normally is good at giving credit, it should be noted).</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link></link>
      <guid></guid>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
